<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Learn Rubix</title>
    <link>http://n1dhn.github.io/learn/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Learn Rubix</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://n1dhn.github.io/learn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Signing up</title>
      <link>http://n1dhn.github.io/learn/signing-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://n1dhn.github.io/learn/signing-up/</guid>
      <description>During the first phase of the pilot, Birdwatch is limited to a small test group in the US.
Our goal is to expand Birdwatch to the global Twitter community. We want anyone to be able to participate and know that having contributors with different points of view is essential to Birdwatch helpfully addressing misinformation. We’ll draw on learnings from this initial test and, over time, scale safely.
Sign up here     Eligibility To become a Birdwatch contributor, accounts must have:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Additional Birdwatch review</title>
      <link>http://n1dhn.github.io/learn/additional-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://n1dhn.github.io/learn/additional-review/</guid>
      <description>What are Birdwatch notes? Birdwatch is a pilot program that allows volunteer contributors on Twitter to collaboratively add context (called “notes”) to Tweets they believe could be misleading. The aim is to keep people on Twitter better informed by showing notes that people from different points of view will find helpful.
Notes are only shown to a small set of people in the pilot program, and notes only appear on Tweets when they’ve been rated helpful by enough people from different points of view.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Downloading data</title>
      <link>http://n1dhn.github.io/learn/download-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://n1dhn.github.io/learn/download-data/</guid>
      <description>We can&amp;rsquo;t wait to learn with you!
All Birdwatch contributions are publicly available on the Download Data page of the Birdwatch site so that anyone in the US has free access to analyze the data, identify problems, and spot opportunities to make Birdwatch better.
If you have questions or feedback about the Birdwatch public data or would like to share your analyses of this data with us, please DM us at @Birdwatch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Examples</title>
      <link>http://n1dhn.github.io/learn/examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://n1dhn.github.io/learn/examples/</guid>
      <description>Great Birdwatch notes follow the program&amp;rsquo;s values: They build understanding, are written in good faith, and are helpful even to those who disagree.
   &amp;ldquo;Whales aren&amp;rsquo;t real&amp;rdquo;   Here&amp;rsquo;s a Tweet making misleading claims about whales, followed by helpful and unhelpful Birdwatch notes:
Whales are not actually mammals. If Humans (land mammals) can’t drink seawater — just try it! — how can supposed sea mammals like whales stay hydrated?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQs</title>
      <link>http://n1dhn.github.io/learn/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://n1dhn.github.io/learn/faq/</guid>
      <description>Who is eligible to participate in the Birdwatch pilot? Is there an approval process?   People in the US can sign up to become contributors in the pilot. Accounts must meet a few criteria to be eligible. Learn more here.
In addition, a small, randomized group of people in the US may see Helpful notes on Tweets, in order to help assess their quality.
In addition to people who have signed up to become Birdwatch contributors, small test groups in the US may see Helpful notes on on Tweets, in order to help assess their quality.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
